fromquarkstoquasars.com 2015-10-13

# Privacy Policy: — From Quarks to Quasars

In the information age, privacy is a concern for everyone, and at From Quarks to Quasars we respect your concerns about the information that we collect. As such, this Privacy Notice is aimed at describing the types of personal information we collect on our websites, how we may use that information, and with whom we may share it. We also tell you how you can reach us to ask general questions, offer comments, inquire about our organization, or get more information about our privacy practices.

## Information We Collect

You may choose to provide personal information (such as your name, email address etc.) on our websites. The ways you may provide information and the types of information you may submit include the following:

  * Purchases: In order to properly process your purchases, you may need to give your email address, full name, billing address and credit card information.
  * Gifts: In order to properly process any gifts, you may need to give the sender full name, sender billing address, sender email address, sender credit card information, recipient full name, recipient billing address, and recipient email address.
  * Blogs: To receive certain updates, you may need to provide your full name and email address.

## How We Use Information We Collect

If we ever need to collect any information, we will use it for the purpose you submitted it. We will not use it to send you other information or products (unless specifically requested by you). We will not use it to send you updates about our site, products,  content we distribute, or other organizations with which we are affiliated. We may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law, (ii) in response to legal process, (iii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials, or (iv) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.

## Links to Other Websites

At times, we may provide links to other websites to source material or provide you with more information. These sites may not be under our control. Your personal information is yours, as we aim to keep it that way. However, From Quarks to Quasars is not responsible for any information collected from or given to any of its affiliates, or to any linked organizations, pages, or individuals. To ensure that your content is being utilized in a manner with which you are comfortable, please check the privacy policy of these respective bodies.

## Updates

By using our services and/or sites you signify your agreement to this Privacy Policy.  Moreover, this Privacy Policy may change at any time. Your continued use of the services and the sites constitutes your acceptance of the any changes that may be made. Please review this statement from time to time to ensure that you are up to date with its most current provisions. For questions or concerns, please contact us at [contact@fromquarkstoquasars.com](mailto:contact@fromquarkstoquasars.com)

The comments, articles, and information on any pages owned by From Quarks to Quasars appear entirely at our discretion. Any content deemed inappropriate will be removed immediately and without notice. Please note that anything you post may be used, along with your name and profile picture. From Quarks to Quasars assumes no responsibility for any information that you post.

By coming to our sites, you acknowledge that you are using our materials at your own risk. From Quarks to Quasars makes no claims that the text, graphics, links, or other items accessed will be error-free, or free of viruses or other harmful components. No advice or information given by From Quarks to Quasars (or any other party on the Web site)) shall create any warranty or liability.

Under no circumstances shall From Quarks to Quasars or any of its affiliates, or their respective partners, be held liable for any damages arising from (or in connection with) your use of the information.

## About Cookies

Cookies are files, often including unique identifiers, that are sent by web servers to web browsers, and which may then be sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies can be used by web servers to identity and track users as they navigate different pages on a website, and to identify users returning to a website.

We may use the information we obtain from your use of our cookies for the following purposes:

  1. to recognise your computer when you visit the website
  2. to track you as you navigate the website, and to enable the use of any e-commerce facilities
  3. to improve the website’s usability
  4. to analyse the use of the website
  5. in the administration of the website
  6. to personalise the website for you, including targeting advertisements which may be of particular interest to you.

Our advertisers and service providers may send you cookies. They may use the information they obtain from your use of their cookies:

  1. to track your browser across multiple websites
  2. to build a profile of your web surfing
  3. to target advertisements which may be of particular interest to you.

If you want to opt-out, download and install the add-on for your web browser.

The Google Analytics opt-out add-on is designed to be compatible with Chrome, Internet Explorer 8-11, Safari, Firefox and Opera. In order to function, the opt-out add-on must be able to load and execute properly on your browser. For Internet Explorer, 3rd-party cookies must be enabled. Learn more about about the opt-out and how to properly install the browser add-on [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881?hl=en).
